(Penny:)- You're kidding.
- No, Raj had to go to the nurse.
(Penny:)Wow. Anything else?
(Leonard:)Mm, the nurse is a woman,
so he couldn't talk to her.
She had to bring him the Grover puppet
so he could point at what hurt. Heh.
(Penny:)Is that it?
(Leonard:)Isn't that enough?
It had weaponized fruit and a puppet.
What more do you want?
(Sheldon(arriving with Alex):)Oh, good. Leonard, you're here.
(Sheldon(arriving with Alex):)Science news. This will interest you.
(Sheldon(arriving with Alex):)And, Penny,
feel free to paint your nails.
- What do you got?
- I believe Alex may have unearthed...
...the grade-school science project that
could be my ticket to the Nobel Prize.
(Sheldon:)Behold.
"Magnets: What Do They Stick To?"
If the answer is metal,
it's not exactly groundbreaking.
The original title was:
"A Rederivation of Maxwell's Equations
Regarding Electromagnetism."
(Sheldon:)I dumbed it down because some
of the more religious people in town...